Guide to the War Poster Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- World War I, 1914-1918; Series I
  - Lafon Allen Collection
    - Great Britain
      - Royal Marine Engineers. Openings for Irishmen, 1918 August; AGB0513; 20x30 inches (Box 71)
      - 1918. Ireland. What Is Your Trade and Where Can It Best Be Utilized?, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0514; 20x30 inches (Box 71)
      - Colonel Lynch's Irish Brigade. Young Men of Ireland, 1918 August; AGB0515; 20x30 inches (Box 71)
      - Colonel Lynch's Irish Brigade. Irishmen Join the Brigade., 1918 August; AGB0516; 20x30 inches (Box 71)
      - Colonel Lynch's Irish Brigade. No Nation Can Live unto Itself., 1918 August; AGB0517; 20x30 inches (Box 71)
      - The Royal Navy Wants Stokers, Seamen, 1918 August; AGB0518; 20x30 inches (Box 71)
      - Let Irishmen Remember. The Sixteenth Division, 1918 August; AGB0519; 20x30 inches (Box 71)
      - Colonel Lynch's Irish Brigade. It Has Started., 1918 August; AGB0520; 20x30 inches (Box 71)
      - Colonel Lynch's Irish Brigade. Join Colonel Lynch, 1918 August; AGB0521; 20x15 inches (Box 71)
      - Lynch's Irish Brigade. The World's Poets, Writers and Statesmen, 1918 August; AGB0522; 20x15 inches (Box 71)
      - Lynch's Brigade. Irishmen. Your Fathers HaveFought for Every Cause., 1918 August; AGB0523; 20x15 inches (Box 71)
      - Triumph Is in Sight. Will This Be Ireland's Triumph?, 1918 September; AGB0524; 20x30 inches (Box 71)
      - Study the Future. Honor Awaits the Man Who Does His Duty, 1918 August; AGB0525; 20x30 inches (Box 71)
      - Study the Future, 1918 August; AGB0526; 20x30 inches (Box 71)
      - A Golden Opportunity Is Offered to Young Irishmen, 1918 August; AGB0527; 20x30 inches (Box 71)
      - A Golden Opportunity Is Offered to Young Irishmen., 1918 August; AGB0528; 20x30 inches (Box 71)
      - Join the Royal Air Force, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0529; 20x30 inches (Box 71)
      - Colonel Lynch's Brigade. Colonel Lynch Does Not Say "Go", 1918 August; AGB0530; 20x30 inches (Box 71)
      - An Irish Rebel's Opinion, 1918 August; AGB0531; 20x30 inches (Box 71)
      - The Royal Irish Regiment. Appeal from the Men to Men of Tipperary., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0532; 20x30 inches (Box 71)
      - Extracts from a Message from the Ulster Division, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0533; 20x30 inches (Box 71)
      - Australia and Ireland, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0534; 20x30 inches (Box 71)
      - To the Men of Munster. Do You Realize that Germany is Making War, 1918 July; AGB0535; 20x30 inches (Box 71)
      - Irish Recruiting. Duty of Irishmen, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0536; 20x30 inches (Box 71)
      - Recruits Required. Age, 18 to 41, 1918 January; AGB0537; 20x30 inches (Box 71)
      - Notice. Men Can Be Accepted for Royal Flying Corps., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0538; 20x30 inches (Box 71)
      - Notice. Men Between the Ages of 18 and 41 Can Be Accepted, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0539; 15x20 inches (Box 71)
      - Increase of Soldiers' Pay and Separation Allowances, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0540; 20x30 inches (Box 71)
      - Separation Allowances for Wives and Children of Soldiers, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0541; 20x30 inches (Box 71)
      - The Tank Corps, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0542; 20x30 inches (Box 71)
      - Some Types of H.M. Army, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0543; 20x30 inches (Box 71)
      - The Allies Want More Men. Join the Quebec Rifles, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0544; 23x33 inches (Box 72)
        Artist: Unknown. Place of Publication: Canada.
      - The Allies Want More Men...Join the Quebec Rifles (French), Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0545; 22x33 inches (Box 72)
      - Canadiens - Francais, Enrollez-vous, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0546; 26x41 inches (Box 72)
      - Les Heros de St. Julien et Festubert, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0547; 24x37 inches (Box 72)
      - The Heros of St. Julien and Festubert., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0548; 24x37 inches (Box 72)
      - Nos Defendrons le Precieux Joyau de la Liberte, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0549; 24x37 inches (Box 72)
      - La Tambour bat; le Clairon Sonne, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0550; 24x37 inches (Box 72)
      - Canadiens-Francais! Le Prussien est encore sure le sol de France, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0551; 20x30 inches (Box 72)
      - Respondez a l'Appel: En ligue, etc., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0552; 25x33 inches (Box 72)
      - If Ye Break Faith, We Shall Not Sleep. I., W.P., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0553; 24x37 inches (Box 72)
      - Get Into Khaki. We Are Dong Our Bit., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0554; 23x33 inches (Box 73)
        Artist: Burton, H.M.. Place of Publication: Australia.
      - Even Up the Roll-Call, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0555; 34x11 inches (Box 73)
        Artist: Unknown. Place of Publication: Australia.
      - It Is More Serious Than You Think. The Barbarian Is Almost, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0556; 25x40 inches (Box 73)
      - Were You There Then?, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0557; 24x36 inches (Box 73)
        Artist: Weston, Harry J.. Place of Publication: Australia.
      - Australia Has Promised Britain 50,000 More Men, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0558; 38x25 inches (Box 73)
      - Australia's Imperishable Record, 1915 May; AGB0559; 25x40 inches (Box 73)
      - Kitchener Says, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0560; 25x40 inches (Box 73)
      - More and Still More Men. Kitchener's Message, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0561; 25x40 inches (Box 73)
      - Can You Fight? The Empire Needs Every Fit Man, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0562; 25x40 inches (Box 73)
      - Get into Khaki. Your Comrades at the Galloipoli are Calling You., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0563; 20x30 inches (Box 73)
      - Pay Your 5L and Help Crush the Germans., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0564; 20x30 inches (Box 74)
      - War Loan, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0565; 20x30 inches (Box 74)
      - Speed the Silver Bullet, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0566; 25x40 inches (Box 74)
      - Help Your Country. Invest, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0567; 20x30 inches (Box 74)
      - Appeal to Women. Make Every Penny Do the Work of Two, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0568; 20x30 inches (Box 74)
      - You Have in Your Pocket, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0569; 20x30 inches (Box 74)
      - If You Buy the New War Loan, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0570; 20x30 inches (Box 74)
      - You Have in Your Pocket Silver Bullets, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0571; 20x30 inches (Box 74)
      - The British Sovereign Will Win, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0572; 20x30 inches (Box 74)
      - War Loan, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0573; 20x30 inches (Box 74)
      - You Can Help to Win, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0574; 20x30 inches (Box 74)
      - Wanted, Men, Munitions, Money, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0575; 20x30 inches (Box 74)
      - Buy War Loan, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0576; 20x30 inches (Box 75)
      - Back Them Up, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0577; 20x30 inches (Box 75)
      - You Can Help to Win the War., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0578; 14x17 inches (Box 75)
      - War Loans, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0579; 20x30 inches (Box 75)
      - 4-1/2% War Loan, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0580; 17x22 inches (Box 75)
      - Turn Your Silver into Bullets, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0581; 20x30 inches (Box 75)
      - Do You Think: Do You Realize: Do You Know, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0582; 20x30 inches (Box 75)
      - War Loan, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0583; 20x30 inches (Box 75)
      - War Loan, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0584; 20x30 inches (Box 75)
      - Lend Your 5 Shilling…and Crush the Germans., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0585; 20x30 inches (Box 75)
      - War and Saving. Every Man and Woman Should Read, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0586; 20x30 inches (Box 75)
      - National Savings Campaign. How You Can Help, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0587; 20x30 inches (Box 75)
      - What Is the Price of One of Your Arms?, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0588; 25x40 inches (Box 76)
      - If You Cannot Fight, Lend Your Money, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0589; 20x30 inches (Box 76)
      - Don't, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0590; 20x30 inches (Box 76)
      - Bad Form in Dress, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0591; 20x30 inches (Box 76)
      - If You Cannot Fight, Lend Your Money, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0592; 20x30 inches (Box 76)
      - L1 for 15-6. Go to the Post Office and Lend Your Money to Your, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0593; 80x120 inches (Box 76)
      - To Dress Extravagantly in War Time is Worse than Bad Form, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0594; 40x60 inches (Box 76)
      - Are You Helping the Germans?, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0595; 40x60 inches (Box 76)
      - 124 Cartridges for 15/6; And Your Money Back with Interest, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0596; 20x30 inches (Box 77)
      - L1 for 15/6, War Saving Certificates, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0597; 20x30 inches (Box 77)
      - L1 for 15/6; to the Men and Women of England, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0598; 40x60 inches (Box 77)
      - L1 for 15/6, up for L387: 10 Shillings, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0599; 20x30 inches (Box 77)
      - 124 Cartridges for 15/6 and Your Money Back, 1916 July; AGB0600; 09x13 inches (Box 77)
      - Six Reasons Why You Should Save, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0601; 22x35 inches (Box 77)
      - Make an Allotment, L1 for 15/6 War Savings Certificates, 1916 September; AGB0602; 09x13 inches (Box 77)
      - A Meeting to Promote the Formation of War Savings Association, 1916 September and October; AGB0603; 08x13 inches (Box 77)
      - National War Savings. A Meeting Will Be Held, 1918 June; AGB0604; 09x13 inches (Box 77)
      - Make a Habit of Buying War Savings Certificates, 1917 April; AGB0605; 09x13 inches (Box 77)
      - A War Savings Association Has Now Been Formed in These Works, 1917 April; AGB0606; 09x13 inches (Box 77)
      - 5% Exchequer Bonds Sold Here, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0607; 10x15 inches (Box 77)
      - Are You Saving for the Children, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0608; 20x30 inches (Box 77)
        Artist: Bylityilis, W.S.. Place of Publication: Great Britain.
      - It's Worth While, That's Why, 1917 September; AGB0609; 20x30 inches (Box 77)
        Artist: Beadle, I.P.. Place of Publication: Great Britain.
      - Buy National War Bonds Today., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0610; 20x30 inches (Box 77)
      - National War Bonds Sold Here, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0611; 13x08 inches (Box 77)
      - Old Age Must Come. So Prepare for it by Investing in War Savings, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0612; 25x39 inches (Box 77)
      - For Your Children. Buy War Savings Certificates, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0613; 39x29 inches (Box 77)
        Artist: Gutti, Rosina M.. Place of Publication: Great Britain.
      - Buy National War Bonds Today., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0614; 60x40 inches (Box 77)
      - A War Savings Association Has Been Formed by this Firm, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0615; 10x15 inches (Box 77)
      - The Story of Democracy's Struggle against Militarism, 1918 November; AGB0616; 10x15 inches (Box 78)
      - The Romantic Life Story of Money and Why We Use It, 1918 October; AGB0617; 10x15 inches (Box 78)
      - The Sea Is God's and He Made It and Britain Keeps It Free, 1918 November; AGB0618; 10x15 inches (Box 78)
      - A War Savings Association Has Been Formed in this Battalion, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0619; 10x15 inches (Box 78)
      - A War Association Has Been Formed by This Firm, 1918 March; AGB0620; 10x15 inches (Box 78)
      - The Story of Britain's Air Supremacy, 1918 November; AGB0621; 10x15 inches (Box 78)
      - Buy National War Bonds Regularly Week by Week., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0622; 40x60 inches (Box 78)
      - It's Safe in National War Bonds, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0623; 20x30 inches (Box 78)
      - Write a Cheque Today for National War Bonds., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0624; 20x30 inches (Box 78)
      - You Buy War Bonds: We Do the Rest, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0625; 20x30 inches (Box 78)
        Artist: Thomas, Bert. Place of Publication: Great Britain.
      - Every Pound Invested in National War Bonds, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0626; 20x30 inches (Box 78)
        Artist: J., A.. Place of Publication: Great Britain.
      - Put It into National War Bonds., 1918 January; AGB0627; 20x30 inches (Box 78)
      - Bomb Them with War Bonds., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0628; 20x30 inches (Box 78)
      - War Bonds. Feed the Guns., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0629; 20x30 inches (Box 78)
      - Buy Your War Bonds Now., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0630; 20x30 inches (Box 78)
      - Joan of Arc Saved France, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0631; 20x30 inches (Box 78)
      - Help to Buy an Aeroplane, 1918 April; AGB0632; 20x30 inches (Box 78)
      - How War Savings Certificates Grow in Value, 1918 April; AGB0633; 20x15 inches (Box 78)
      - Buy National War Bonds Now. Stamp it on Your Memory., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0634; 20x30 inches (Box 78)
      - Fight with National War Bonds., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0635; 20x30 inches (Box 78)
      - England Expects, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0636; 15x20 inches (Box 79)
        Artist: Franks, William J.. Place of Publication: Great Britain.
      - Sam Brierly of the National Union of Railway Men, 1918 May; AGB0637; 20x30 inches (Box 79)
      - Up Civilians! Send Your Money into the Fight, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0638; 15x20 inches (Box 79)
      - Back Him Up, Buy War Bonds., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0639; 60x40 inches (Box 79)
      - Put Strength in the Final Blow. Buy War Bonds, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0640; 40x60 inches (Box 79)
      - To Prevent This- Buy War Savings Certificates Now., 1918 June; AGB0641; 25x40 inches (Box 79)
        Artist: Brown, F. Gregory. Place of Publication: Great Britain.
      - Safe as the British Empire. National War Bonds., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0642; 20x30 inches (Box 79)
      - Their Home! Belgium 1918. Buy National War Bonds., 1918 May; AGB0643; 25x40 inches (Box 79)
      - For Her! Buy War Savings Certificates, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0644; 20x30 inches (Box 79)
      - War Weapons Week. Help to Swell the Total for the Week, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0645; 20x15 inches (Box 79)
      - Buy War Bonds Now., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0646; 20x30 inches (Box 79)
      - You Get More Than He Does; What Are You Doing with the Difference?, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0647; 15x20 inches (Box 79)
      - Take Part of Your Change in War Savings Stamps, 1918 August; AGB0648; 09x09 inches (Box 79)
      - Paid Off, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0649; 20x30 inches (Box 79)
      - Paid Off, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0650; 14x20 inches (Box 79)
      - Now; Back the Bayonets with Your War Savings Certificates, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0651; 20x30 inches (Box 80)
      - War Savings Stamps, 1918 August; AGB0652; 15x20 inches (Box 80)
      - War Savings Stamps, 1918 August; AGB0653; 20x30 inches (Box 80)
      - Buy War Bonds Now., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0654; 20x30 inches (Box 80)
      - Write a Check Today for National War Bonds., 1918 May; AGB0655; 08x12 inches (Box 80)
      - Feed the Guns with War Bonds and Help to End the War., 1918 August; AGB0656; 20x30 inches (Box 80)
      - Turn Your Money into War Bonds., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0657; 20x30 inches (Box 80)
      - Feeds the Guns with War Bonds and Help to Bring Them Down., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0658; 20x30 inches (Box 80)
      - Feed the Guns with War Bonds and Help to End the War., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0659; 20x30 inches (Box 80)
      - Feed the Guns with War Bonds, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0660; 20x30 inches (Box 80)
      - Feed the Guns with War Bonds and Help to End the War., 1917 March; AGB0661; 75x58 inches (Box 80)
      - Feed the Guns with War Bonds and Help to End the War., 1917 March; AGB0662; 75x112 inches (Box 80)
      - Feed the Guns with War Bonds and Help to End the War., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0663; 20x30 inches (Box 80)
      - Money is Still Needed, so Keep on Buying War Bonds., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0664; 20x30 inches (Box 80)
      - Feed the Guns with War Bonds and Help to End the War., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0665; 20x30 inches (Box 80)
      - Feed the Guns with War Bonds and Help to End the War., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0666; 13x13 inches (Box 80)
      - Feed the Guns with War Bonds and Help to End the War., 1918 October; AGB0667; 20x30 inches (Box 80)
        Artist: Stanley, Sidney. Place of Publication: Great Britain.
      - To the Guns., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0668; 48x08 inches (Box 80)
      - Money is Still Needed. Keep on Buying War Bonds., 1918 December; AGB0669; 20x30 inches (Box 80)
      - Your Last Chance. War Bonds Will Be Withdrawn on January 18th, 1918 December; AGB0670; 20x30 inches (Box 80)
      - A Plain Duty, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0671; 13x20 inches (Box 80)
        Artist: Pegram, Frederick. Place of Publication: Great Britain.
      - A Plain Duty, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0672; 20x30 inches (Box 80)
      - Buy National War Bonds Regularly, Week by Week., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0673; 10x15 inches (Box 80)
      - Appeal to the Scottish People. The Tide of War Has Turned, 1916 September-1917 February; AGB0674; 18x20 inches (Box 81)
      - The War Savings. Public Meeting, 1916 October-1917 April; AGB0675; 17x27 inches (Box 81)
      - Our Cause Is Just, 1917 April; AGB0676; 20x30 inches (Box 81)
        Artist: Forde. Place of Publication: Great Britain.
      - A War Savings Association Has Been Formed, 1917 April-1918 February; AGB0677; 21x32 inches (Box 81)
      - The Necessity of Today Is to Invest in National War Bonds, 1917 October; AGB0678; 21x32 inches (Box 81)
      - Save Life and Liberty Which Are In Peril., 1917 November; AGB0679; 23x35 inches (Box 81)
      - Those Who Are Not Fighting for Their Country Should Save for It., 1917 November; AGB0680; 22x34 inches (Box 81)
      - You Can Hasten Peace, Buy 5% National War Bonds, 1917 December; AGB0681; 20x30 inches (Box 81)
      - Back Up Your Fighting Men and the Tank, 1918 January; AGB0682; 23x35 inches (Box 81)
      - War Weapons Week, April 8-13th. Help to Provide These War Weapons, 1918 March; AGB0683; 20x30 inches (Box 81)
      - War Weapons Week, 1918 March; AGB0684; 20x30 inches (Box 81)
      - War Weapons Week, 1918 March; AGB0685; 20x30 inches (Box 81)
      - War Weapons Week, 1918 March; AGB0686; 20x30 inches (Box 81)
      - War Weapons Week, 1918 March; AGB0687; 20x30 inches (Box 81)
      - War Weapons Week, 1918 March; AGB0688; 20x30 inches (Box 81)
      - War Weapons Week, 1918 March; AGB0689; 20x30 inches (Box 81)
      - Help to Defend Your Life and Liberty, 1918 March; AGB0690; 20x30 inches (Box 81)
      - War Weapons Week, April 8-13th. To Scottish Farmers, 1918 April; AGB0691; 21x30 inches (Box 81)
      - Scots, Wha Ha'e, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0692; 20x30 inches (Box 81)
      - Your Money or Their Lives, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0693; 20x30 inches (Box 82)
      - Your Money or Their Lives, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0694; 09x14 inches (Box 82)
      - 124 Cartridges for 15-6 and Your Money Back with Interest, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0695; 80x120 inches (Box 82)
      - Victory War Loan, Metropolitan Campaign, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0696; 20x30 inches (Box 82)
      - War Savings Certificates Sold Here, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0697; 12x05 inches (Box 82)
      - War Savings Association in His Majesty's Ships, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0698; 19x29 inches (Box 82)
      - War Savings Stamps Sold Here, 1918 August; AGB0699; 10x10 inches (Box 82)
      - Take Part of Your Change in War Savings Stamps, 1918 August; AGB0700; 10x10 inches (Box 82)
      - Our L2,500,000 Super-Dreadnaught. You Can Help, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0701; 30x80 inches (Box 82)
      - Our Cruiser. You Can Help. Buy War Bonds. Business Men's Week, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0702; 30x80 inches (Box 82)
      - Our L100,000 Submarine, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0703; 30x80 inches (Box 82)
      - Our L250,000 Monitor, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0704; 30x80 inches (Box 82)
      - Our L150,000 Destroyer, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0705; 30x80 inches (Box 82)
      - The Tank Will Be in Islington on March 11th and 12th, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0706; 20x30 inches (Box 82)
      - London's Week. Your Can Help. Buy War Bonds., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0707; 20x30 inches (Box 82)
      - London's Week. Your Can Help. Buy War Bonds., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0708; 15x20 inches (Box 82)
      - Our Cruiser. You Can Help. Buy War Bonds., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0709; 15x20 inches (Box 82)
      - Our Aeroplanes. You Can Help. Buy War Bonds., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0710; 15x20 inches (Box 82)
      - Our L250,000 Monitor. You Can Help. Buy War Bonds., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0711; 15x20 inches (Box 82)
      - Our L150,000 Destroyer. You Can Help. Buy War Bonds., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0712; 15x20 inches (Box 82)
      - Our L100,000 Submarine. You Can Help. Buy War Bonds., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0713; 15x20 inches (Box 82)
      - Men on the March., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0715; 25x40 inches (Box 82)
      - Thumbs Up., 1918 June 7; AGB0716; 20x30 inches (Box 83)
      - Smokes for Wounded Soldiers and Sailors, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0717; 12x17 inches (Box 83)
      - Blue Cross Poster. Our Dumb Friends League, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0718; 20x30 inches (Box 83)
      - Our Dumb Friends League. Blue Cross Fund., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0719; 20x30 inches (Box 83)
      - Blue Cross Fund. Help the Wounded Horses at the War., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0720; 20x30 inches (Box 83)
      - Our Dumb Friends League., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0721; 20x30 inches (Box 83)
      - Our Day; The British Red Cross Society and Order of St. John, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0722; 20x30 inches (Box 83)
        Artist: Purvis, Tom.. Place of Publication: Great Britain.
      - The Sailors Day., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0723; 20x30 inches (Box 83)
      - Most Urgent of All Funds…British Red Cross Society, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0724; 20x30 inches (Box 83)
        Artist: Purvis, Tom. Place of Publication: Great Britain.
      - British Red Cross and the Order of St. John; Our Day, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0725; 20x30 inches (Box 83)
      - County of London Red Cross Fair, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0726; 20x30 inches (Box 83)
      - St. Patrick's Day, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0727; 20x30 inches (Box 83)
      - Mesopotamia Day, Friday, April 13th: In Aid of the Mesopotamia, 1917 April 13; AGB0728; 20x30 inches (Box 83)
        Artist: Dickson, D.J.A.; Carter, Rena R.. Place of Publication: Great Britain.
      - Mesopotamia Day, Friday, April 13th, 1917, 1917 April 13; AGB0729; 20x30 inches (Box 83)
      - Lieutenant-General Sir Stanley Maud Telegraphed From Bagdad, 1917 March 30; AGB0730; 20x30 inches (Box 83)
      - Navy Week, July 23-28., AGB0731; 20x30 inches (Box 83)
      - National Baby Week, July 2-7, July 23-28; AGB0732; 20x30 inches (Box 83)
        Artist: Scott, Septimus E.. Place of Publication: Great Britain.
      - National Baby Week, July 2-7, AGB0733; 20x30 inches (Box 83)
      - National Baby Week., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0734; 40x60 inches (Box 84)
      - In Aid of the Lord Roberts Memorial Workshops, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0735; 20x30 inches (Box 84)
        Artist: Tyler.. Place of Publication: Great Britain.
      - July 6, The Silent Tribute to Lord Roberts, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0736; 20x30 inches (Box 84)
      - The Silent Tribute to Lord Roberts, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0737; 15x09 inches (Box 84)